{
    "id": "4c0d134162f647c8a4399c7fc51a3f90",
    "title": "Many or much",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d5810473297b42ef96460d916d6ee962",
            "title": "Many or Much",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It has been raining for ………………. days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We didn’t do ……………….. work yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has …………………. friends.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A small car does not use ………………. fuel.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There aren’t ……………… apples on the tree.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ……………… money do you need?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been to Australia ……………….. times.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know ………………. about computers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ………………. people are there waiting outside?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He can speak ………………. languages.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There isn’t …………………. water in this pond.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have to hurry. I don’t have ………………… time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}